A Guide to the Lottie Chaikin Plaut papers FA1743
Rockefeller Archive Center
Lottie Chaikin Plaut papers
1942-2006
Rockefeller Archive Center
Plaut, Lottie Chaikin
FA1743
0.66 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box and 1 half-letter document box
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
This small collection of papers includes diaries, memoirs, health bulletins and reports, primarily from the 1940s and 1950s.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
- Monthly Diaries, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Monthly Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Planning Reports - School of Nursing of the State of Rio de Janiero, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- SESP and Nursing School - Health Bulletins, 1942-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1950-2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Oral History Memoir, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Personal File, 1943-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Publications - Association of Inter-American Affairs - Bulletins and Articles, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Publications - CIAA Health and Sanitations Newsletter, 1943-1950 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1944-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Sobrel, Vera - Research Papers (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Teixeira, Carol Reno - Oral History Memoir, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Photographs, 1943-1944; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)